shoplately.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

Here at ShopLately we recognize that your privacy is very important, and to keep you informed about our privacy practices we ask that you please read the guidelines described below. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of information about you that is gathered through ShopLately.com (the “Site”). We collect two types of information: personal and anonymous information. “Personal Information” includes information about you that is personably identifiable, such as your name, email address, or other non-public information. “Anonymous Information” includes your Internet Protocol (IP) address, time and date of Site access, and other information that does not allow for the identification of an individual. Keep in mind that because ShopLately is a growing website and internet technologies are constantly evolving, these guidelines are subject to change and any said changes will be posted on this page. 

#### User Consent

By accessing or otherwise using the Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, which are incorporated into the Site’s terms and conditions (http://ShopLately.com/info/terms). You expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of both your Personal and Anonymous information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### Age

You must be 18 years of age or older to use this site. If you are 13 years of age or older but not yet 18, you may only use this site in conjunction with your parent or legal guardian, who agrees to the terms of this Privacy Policy. ShopLately does not intentionally collect the personal information of children under 13 years of age, and will remove any and all of a user’s personal information if we discover he or she is under 13. By using the Site, you represent that you are over the age of 18 or are between 13 and 18 and using the Site in conjunction with your parent or legal guardian. 

#### Personal Information You Provide

In the course of using this site, you will provide us with some information about yourself. For example, when you register for an account on ShopLately.com, you will be asked to provide your name, email address and gender. Similarly, when you make a purchase, you will be asked to provide credit card information, shipping and billing addresses, and other information as may be necessary. You also may choose to upload photos and content to the Site, leave feedback, write reviews, submit ratings or other information. ShopLately will collect all such information, and any other information that you voluntarily post the Site or otherwise submit to us. We also may receive other personal information about you from third parties who you have registered with or otherwise volunteered information to. We may associate information from third parties with information we have gathered about you. 

Personal information gathered about you may be used to complete transactions, notify you of special offers from ShopLately.com or third parties, update you on changes to ShopLately’s policies, and shared with third parties you purchase products from to facilitate the delivery of those products. We may also share personal information with third parties to improve your experience with the Site and ShopLately. These third parties may include, but are not limited to, companies that facilitate business operations and marketing services for ShopLately. Your personal information will never be sold. 

#### Anonymous Data

ShopLately collects information from you that cannot be used to personally identify you, such as IP addresses. We also collect data on the types of internet browsers and operating systems that access the Site, page views, navigational patterns, and Site use trends. This data is used to improve your experience on the site and ShopLately’s interaction with its visitors. Anonymous data may be shared with third parties.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small files stored on your computer containing information sent by websites you have visited. The Site may use both session cookies (cookies that expire when you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (cookies the remain on your computer until you delete them). Cookies can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site, and they allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most internet browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature. But you should note that cookies may be necessary to access certain parts and functions of the Site.

#### Security

The safety of your personal information is of the utmost important to us. We therefore implement necessary physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your personal information from misuse, loss, or alteration. 

#### External Links

The Site has links to third party websites, some associated with ShopLately, some not. This Privacy Policy does not extend or cover those third party websites, and ShopLately is not responsible for how those websites use information, personal or otherwise, that you provide them with. When you click on a link to a third party website, you do so at your own risk. You should carefully review the privacy policy of any website you visit.

#### Email

As discussed above, we will collect your email address if you voluntarily submit it to us by registering for a ShopLately account. If you send an email to us regarding any matter, we will collect your email address along with the contents of your email, including any attachments. We may use your email address to contact you regarding your account, purchases you’ve made, changes to this Privacy Policy or the Site’s terms and conditions, special offers from third parties, messages from merchants associated with the Site, and any other purpose useful in conducting business with you. You can opt-out of receiving marketing emails from ShopLately by clicking on the “unsubscribe” button at the bottom of emails we send you. We will never sell your e-mail address to other companies or organizations, and your account password will always remain protected.

#### Modification

ShopLately may at its sole discretion modify, amend or edit this Privacy Policy at anytime. Changes to this policy will be posted here, therefore you should regularly review this webpage so that you are aware of our current privacy practices. Changes will be effective on the date they are posted here. If you do not wish to be bound by the changes made to this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Site.
